Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
- Series IV. Bear History Project
  - Bear Icons
    - Bear Icon Artists
      - Angell, A.M. (Box 29)
      - Auerbach, Scott (Box 29)
      - Barrow, Randy (Box 29)
      - Behrmann, Kurt von (Box 29)
      - Bianchi, Agostino (Box 29)
      - Blake, Nayland (Box 29)
      - Both, Markus ("Germanbear"/Saarbrücken) (Box 29)
      - Braswell, Richard (Box 29)
      - Brooks, Michael ("Sargebear") (Box 29)
      - Brown, Tony C. (Box 30)
      - Bruce, Neil (Box 30)
        Two Folders
      - Bryk, Dwayne (Box 30)
      - Buchholz, Keith A., 2000-2003 (Box 30)
      - Cardella, Normand (Box 30)
      - Celso Junior (Switzerland) (Box 30)
      - Chester, Mark I. (Box 30)
      - Costilla, Damian (Box 30)
      - Cropper, Andy (Box 30)
      - Curry, John, 2001 (Box 30)
      - delPo, Cen ("Ken") (Box 30)
      - Drew, Dan (Box 30)
      - Duncan, Marc (Box 30)
      - Easton, Steve (Box 30)
      - Erikson, Carl, 2004-2005 (Box 30)
      - Eves, Bruce (Box 30)
      - Ferrugio, Richard (Box 30)
      - Fiorenza, Jay (Box 30)
      - Fischer, Lee (Box 30)
      - Fontenot, Heyd, 2002 (Box 30)
      - Fotobaer.de (Klaus) (Box 30)
      - Frazer, John (Box 30)
      - Frisch, Fran (Box 30)
      - Gatto, Jon (Box 30)
      - Goecke, Tim (Box 30)
      - Gomez, Luis (Box 30)
      - Greig, David (Box 30)
      - Hamilton, David (Box 30)
      - Hatch, Richard ("SurvivorBear") (Box 30)
      - Hay, Bob (Box 30)
      - Hoshikawa, Michio (Box 30)
      - Hurlbut, Tom (Box 30)
      - Kendall, D. (Box 30)
      - Komater, Chris (Box 30)
      - Lago, Ramon (Box 30)
      - Lopez, Ali (Box 30)
      - Lucente, Giulio (Box 30)
      - Ludwig, Lynn (Box 30)
      - Macias, Loren (Box 30)
      - Maidel, Bob (Box 30)
      - McWeeney, Brendan (Box 30)
      - Murphy, Rob ("Bertbear") (Box 30)
      - Norris, T.J. (Box 30)
      - Nyitray, Alan (Box 30)
      - O'Connor, Michael Patrick (Box 30)
      - Perez, Rafi (Box 30)
      - Polipo, Zio (Ferraro, Marco), 2000 (Box 30)
      - Rand, John (Box 30)
        Three Folders
      - Rand, John (Box 74)
      - Riccoboni, Rand D. (Box 74)
      - Roberts, Paul (Box 74)
      - Robinson, Walter (Box 74)
      - Rushart, Steve (Box 74)
      - Sawtell, David ("Jugga") (Box 74)
      - Scibetta, Joe (Box 74)
      - Sheffer, Blaine (Box 74)
      - Siedler, Jeffery, 2002 (Box 74)
      - Small, David, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
      - Sutton, Stephen Jaye (Box 74)
      - Tattelman, Ira, 2001-2002 (Box 74)
      - Taylor, Chris (Box 74)
      - Thorn, Mike (Box 74)
      - Stefano ("Viste", Italy) (Box 74)
      - Weir, Anthony (Box 74)
      - Zinovjev, Dmitrij (Box 74)
  - Bear Icons exhibition Gallery Book
    - Collective Artists' Work 1984-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
    - Art and Artifacts, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 5-9)
    - Bears Icons and Beyond:Homomasculinities around the world and evolving exhibition, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 10-13)
    - Homomacho:Disruptive Masculinities, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 14-16)
    - Bears 101:The Rise of a Gay Male Identity, Subculture, and Community,1986 to today. (Box 61, Folder 17-18)
    - B12 Exhibition:Slides (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Bear Icons and Beyond IV:Washington, DC.Master Price List (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Bear Icons and Beyond IV:Washington, DC.Pictures (Box 61, Folder 21-22)
    - Bears:Icons of Gay Male Masculinity (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Italian article about the exhibition (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - B12 Exhibition Pictures (Box 61, Folder 25-26)
    - La fiesta de los osos pictures (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Cards (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Ephemera
    - Bear Pride T-Shirts (Box 32-33)
    - Bear Boxers (Box 32)
    - Bear Pride Baseball Hats (Box 32-33)
    - Bear Mugs (Box 34-35)
    - Handkerchiefs (Box 34-35)
    - Bear Rendezvous Framed Pins, 1995-2000 (Box 68)
    - Framed Photographs, n.d., 1993, 1994 (Box 68)
    - Bear Conference and Membership Pens (Box 68)
    - Bear Conference Badges, including Octobearfest, Bear Expo, and Bear Invasion, 1992, 1994, 1996, 1997, 2000, 2002 (Box 68)
    - International Bear Rendezvous Badges, 1995-1998, 2000, 2007 (Box 68)
    - Assorted Business Cards (Box 68)
    - Bear Organization Membership Cards (Box 68)
    - Stickers (Box 68)
    - International Bear Rendezvous Notebook, 1996 (Box 68)
    - Conference Souvenirs, 1995-2000 (Box 68)
    - Conference Ephemera (Box 68)
    - Assorted Postcards and Quartercards (Box 68)
    - Bear Icons Postcard, 1999 (Box 68)
    - Bear Icons: Art and Artifacts Postcard, March 6-19, 2001 (Box 68)
    - Bear Icons and Beyond Postcard, 2001 (Box 68)
    - Bear Icons and Beyond IV Postcard, 2002 (Box 68)
    - Homo/Macho: Disruptive Masculinities Postcards, 2004 (Box 68)
    - Queer Masculinities Program, Mount Ida College, Newton Centre, MA Pamphlet, April 20-22, 2000 (Box 68)
    - Anthology II: Long Playing, written by Eric Franklin Crow, 2006; CD-960 (Box 68)
    - Handkerchief (Box 68)
    - International Bear Rendezvous Bag (Box 68)
    - Certificate of authenticity and letter Re: Les Wright garment, August 1999 (Box 68)
    - Authentic garment (Box 68)
    - Bear Conference Pins, including Bear Expo, International Bear Rendezvous, Regional Organizations, etc. (Box 69)
  - Billy Club Files
    - Fund Raising (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Grant, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Activities (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Billy Times, 2007-2008 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Board of Director, July 2007 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Billy Gathering, July 2007 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Gathering, Labor Day 2007 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Gathering, Halloween 2007 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Gathering, December 2009 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Gathering, February 2008 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Gathering, May Day 2008 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Gathering, July Fourth 2008 (Box 54, Folder 12-13)
    - Gathering, August 2008 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Gathering, Halloween 2008 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Gathering, New Year's Eve 2008 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Gathering, May Day 2009 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Gathering, July Fourth 2009 (Box 54, Folder 18-20)
    - Gathering, Labor Day 2009 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Gathering, Halloween 2009 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Gathering, New Year's Eve 2009 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Oral History, Ron Vanscoyk, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Postcards (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Gay Men's Community Initiative:Cards (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - San Francisco Gay Men's Community Initiative (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Easton Mountain Catalogs (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Articles (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Articles for Voice Male, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Billy Gathering, February 2010 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Billy Community, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Photos
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 6-13)
    - Empire Bear, Rochester, NY, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Bear Book II, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - BHP Nashoba, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 18-21)
    - Naked Les Wright (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - John Topping's Postcard (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Ned and Chris, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Bear Icons Postcards (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Naked Men (Box 57, Folder 5-6)
    - Bear Icons Exhibition (slides) (Box 57, Folder 7-10)
    - International Bear Rendezvous (negatives), 1995 (Box 57, Folder 11-14)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 15-20 (negatives))
    - International Bear Rendezvous (negatives), 1998 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Ned and Chris (negatives), 2000 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Bear Expo photo album, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Bear Expo photo album, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Stonewall 25 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
    - South Bay Bear Pair Alto's, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - New York City, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Londfellow House, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Bear Weekend-Hillside Campgrounds, Pa, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Bhp Archival-Fictburg, Ma, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Mr. Bear New England Contest, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 12-13)
    - Summer Bear Wech-Provincetown, RI, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 14-18)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 19-22)
    - Travels in New England, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Summer Bear Wech-Provincetown, RI, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 24-30)
    - Bear Games-Provincetown, RI, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 31-33)
    - Monty Bears Harvest Fest, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - New York City, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 35-40)
    - San Francisco, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Visit Ric Keanel in Vermont, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Monty Bears, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - New York State Travel, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Monty Bears, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Texas Bear Round Up 007-Dallas, TX, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Stonewall 25 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - San Francisco B/W (Box 60, Folder 48-54)
    - San Francisco (Box 60, Folder 55-57)
    - Loose Photos (Box 60, Folder 58-59)
    - Bear Icons: Art and Artifacts Notebook (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Scott LaGreen and Jim Photos, circa 2000-2001; CD - ??? (Box 68)
    - Boston Gay Pride Parade, June 1997 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Les Wright Publicity Stills, November 1999 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Mr. Bear New England Contest, September 2000 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - IBR 2000 Photos, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - IBR 2001 Photos, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Bear Book II and Bear Handbook, San Francisco, February 2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Town Cemetary, Provincetown, MA, August 2002 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Les Wright and Dale Holiday Card, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Les Wright Photos and Postcards (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Les Wright Nude Photos (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Art Quality Photo/Postcards (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Large Landscape Photographs (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Large Photographs (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Holiday Card from Les and Dale, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Photo Cropping and Editing (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Photos - Agostino Biachi, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Photos - Paul Roberts, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Photos - Norman Cardella, 1994-1997 (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Photos - David Greig (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Photos - John Rand (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Photos - Anthony Weir (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Photos - Damien Costilla (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Photo Album and Negatives - Bear Week? (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Negatives
    - Negatives, 1981-1988 (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Negatives, 1988-1996 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Negatives, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - Negatives, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - Negatives, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 65-71)
    - Negatives, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 72-76)
    - Negatives, Christmas (Box 60, Folder 77)
    - Negatives-Muny Subway:Poster Billboard B/W (Box 60, Folder 78)
    - Negatives-Nudes (Box 60, Folder 79)
    - Negatives-San Francisco (Box 60, Folder 80-81)
    - Negatives-Views of Interiors B/W (Box 60, Folder 82)
    - Loose Negatives (Box 60, Folder 83-85)
    - Postcards (Box 60, Folder 86)
    - Miscellanea (Box 60, Folder 87)
    - Spring, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 88)
    - Negatives - Agostino Bianchi, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 89)
    - Negatives - Chris Komater, 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 90)
    - Negatives - T. J. Norris (Box 60, Folder 91)
    - Negatives - Rand Riccoboni - Summer Bear Week Provincetown, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 92)
    - Negatives - Neil Bruce (Box 60, Folder 93)
    - Negatives - Tony C. Brown, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 94)
    - Negatives - John Rand (Box 60, Folder 95)
    - Negatives - David Greig - BCA (Box 60, Folder 96)
    - Negatives - Kurt von Behrmann - BCA (Box 60, Folder 97)
    - Negatives - Anthony Weir, 1985-1996 (Box 60, Folder 98)
    - Negatives - Carl Erikson (Box 60, Folder 99)
    - "Nashoba Country" Negatives, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Assorted Slides (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Les Wright's Friends Slides (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Nudes Slides (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Landscapes Slides (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Paintings Slides (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Steve Albert and Scott LaBrera (Nudes) Slides (Box 72, Folder 21-22)
    - Miscellaneous Slides (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Ned and Chris Slides (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - IBR 2000, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Boston Gay Pride Parade, June 1997 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - IBR 2001, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Bear Book II and Bear Handbook (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Mr. Bear New England Contest, September 2000 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Les Wright Publicity Stills, November 1999 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Calendars
    - Calendars, 2000-2010 (Box 58)
    - Calendars, 1994-2005 (Box 59)
    - Article about Calendars (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Bear Clipping Files
    - Bear Clipping: Advocate, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Bear Clipping: AIDS, 1987, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Bear Clipping: Andros Studio, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Bear Clipping: Arena, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Bear Clipping: Athletes, 1990-2002 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Bear Clipping: Baseball, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Bear Clipping: The Bearatones, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Circuit: Lazy Bear, 2000,2002,2007 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Bear Clipping: Beards, 1960s (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Bear Clipping: Beards (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Bear Clipping: Beards (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Bear Clipping: "Bear in Mind" Radio Show, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Bear Clipping: Bears (the Animal), 1990s (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Bear Clipping: Cartoons, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Bear Clipping: Personals Websites, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Bear Clipping: Belfast Bears, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Bear Clipping: Belfast Bears - Photos for BHP website, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 17-20)
    - Bear Clipping: Bikers and Bad Boys, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Bear Clipping: Blue-Collar and Working-Class, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Bear Clipping: Body and Body Image, 1997-2003 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Bear Clipping: Body Modification/Piercing, Branding (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Bear Clipping: Brush Creek Media and Bear Magazine, 1992, 1997, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Bear Clipping: Canadian Bears, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Bear Clipping: Jair Aki Mikael Choklat Dissertation: "Bears: A Sub-Culture or Mainstream Phenomena, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Bear Clipping: Chest, 1985, 1996, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Bear Clipping: Hirsute Club Notecards, 1983-1985 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Bear Clipping: CR Magazine, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Bear Clipping: Civil War 4 Gay Bi Men, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Bear Clipping: Codes, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Bear Clipping: Colt Studios Magazines, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Bear Clipping: Colt Studios Magazines, 1972, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Bear Clipping: Cowboys (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Bear Clipping: Cowboy Postcards (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Bear Clipping: DaDe/Ursus (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Bear Clipping: Dragonfly (Symbol, Icon), 2007 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Bear Clipping: Drummer, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Bear Clipping: Fat (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Bear Clipping: Flags, 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Bear Clipping: Football, 2002, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Bear Clipping: Fox Studios, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Bear Clipping: French Bears, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Bear Clipping: German Bears, 1997, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Bear Clipping: German Bears, 1992, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Bear Clipping: German Bears, 1997, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Bear Clipping: Goatboy and the Music Machines, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Bear Clipping: Heyl, Steve, 1993, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 49)
    - Bear Clipping: Hirsute History, 1959, 1981-2, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 50)
    - Bear Clipping: India and South Asians, 1986-1996 (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Bear Clipping: In Touch (Box 70, Folder 52)
    - Bear Clipping: Kake (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - Bear Clipping: Kelso, Steve, 1994, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - Bear Clipping: Kilts, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 55)
    - Bear Clipping: Leather, 1980-1990s (Box 70, Folder 56)
    - Bear Clipping: Leather, 1980, 1997, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 57)
    - Bear Clipping: Literature and Fiction, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 58)
    - Bear Clipping: Lurch, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 59)
    - Bear Clipping: Man 2 Man, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 60)
    - Bear Clipping: ManDate, 1985, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 61)
    - Bear Clipping: Marines, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 62)
    - Bear Clipping: Masculinism, 1990s-2000s (Box 70, Folder 63)
    - Bear Clipping: McQuade, Mack, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 64)
    - Bear Clipping: Muscle Bears (Box 70, Folder 65)
    - Bear Clipping: Neff, Wade, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 66)
    - Bear Clipping: Nude, Nudism, Nudity, 1990-2000 (Box 70, Folder 67)
    - Bear Clipping: Palmer, Joseph (Box 70, Folder 68)
    - Bear Clipping: Joe Palmer's Gravesite Photos (Box 70, Folder 69)
    - Bear Clipping: Rofes, Eric, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 70)
    - Bear Clipping: Radical Faeries, 1994, 1995, 1998, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 71)
    - Bear Clipping: Radical Faeries, 2000, 2001, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 72)
    - Bear Clipping: Radcliffe, Jack, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 73)
    - Bear Clipping: Provincetown, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 74)
    - Bear Clipping: Policarpio, Joe, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 75)
    - Bear Clipping: Playgirl, 1975, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 76)
    - Bear Clipping: Piercing World (Box 70, Folder 77)
    - Bear Clipping: Penis, 1990-2000 (Box 70, Folder 78)
    - Bear Clipping: Palmieri, Francesco Warbear (Box 70, Folder 79)
    - Bear Clipping: Santas, 1995, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 80)
    - Bear Clipping: Smokey Bear, 1970s, 1980s, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 81)
    - Bear Clipping: Smokey Bear, 1994-2003 (Box 70, Folder 82)
    - Bear Clipping: Target, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 83)
    - Bear Clipping: Square-Dancing, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 84)
    - Bear Clipping: Tatoos, 1990s-2000s (Box 70, Folder 85)
    - Bear Clipping: Whitman, Walt, 2000, 2002, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Bear Clipping: Wrestling, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Bear Clipping: Wright, Les, 2000s (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Bear Clipping: Wright, Les, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Bear Clipping: Wright, Les (Photos) (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Bear Clipping: Tom of Finland (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Bear Clipping: ZZ Top, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Bear Clipping: IBR 2006, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Bear Clipping: IBR 2007, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Bear Clipping: IBR 2007 Publications, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Bear Clipping: IBR 2008, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 11-13)
    - Bear Clipping: Teaching a Course on Men, 1980s (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Bear Clipping: Paper: "Capitalist Development: Creator of Masculinity and Destroyer of Patriarchy?" by John MacInnes, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Bear Clipping: "Male Feminism" by Stephen Heath, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Bear Clipping: "Outlaws: Gay Men in Feminism" by Craig Owens, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Bear Clipping: Paper: "Redefining Men: Alternative Masculinities in a Twelve Step Program" by Leslie Irvine and Brian Klocke, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear-Related Media, 1995-1997 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Ephemera, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Bear Clipping: Smalley, Luke, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Bear Clipping: "The Complete Bear.com" and "Bear Community" Wikipedia Page and other Digital Media, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Bear Clipping: Oxborough, Paul G, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Bear Clipping: Nerdrum, Odd, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Bear Clipping: Bears of San Francisco (BOSF), 2006 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Bear Clipping: Bears of San Francisco (BOSF), 2007 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Bear Clipping: Body Image Workshop, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Bear Clipping: Syllabus: "Masculinity and the Novel" course taught by Lisa Blansett, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Bear Clipping: Syllabus: "History of Manhood in America, 1750-1940" course taught by Prof. Bruce Dorsey, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Bear Clipping: Syllabus: "Narrative and Culture", 1999 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Bear Clipping: Critique of Commodity Aesthetics by Wolfgang Fritz Haug, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Bear Clipping: Manliness and Civilization by Gail Bederman, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Bear Clipping: "For a Sociology of teh Body: An Analytical Review" by Arthur W. Frank, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Bear Clipping: "Theorizing Masculinities in Contemporary Social Science" by Scott Coltrane, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Bear Clipping: "A Very Delicate and Difficult Subject: Orthodox and Respectable Views on Sex to 1920" by Leslie A Hall, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Bear Clipping: "Evil Companions, Scarlet Women and Pernicious Quacks: The Subcultures of Sex", by Leslie A Hall, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Bear Clipping: "Homosexual Scandal and Compulsory Heterosexuality in the 1890s" by Dellamora, Richard, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Bear Clipping: "Male Sport" by Roger Horrocks, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Bear Clipping: "Psychoanalysis on Masculinity" by R.W. Connell, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Bear Clipping: "Masculinity as Signs" by Diana Saco, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Bear Clipping: "The Third Body: Patterns in the Construction of the Subject in Gay Male Narrative Film" by Thomas Waugh, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Bear Clipping: "Men's Bodies" by R.W. Connell, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Bear Clipping: "Macho Love: Romantic Films for Men" by Japhy Grant, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Bear Clipping: Images that Injure by Paul Martin Lester, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Bear Clipping: "Coming Out Against the War: Antimilitarism and the Politicization of Homosexuality in the Era of Vietnam" by Justin David Suran, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - Bear Clipping: "The Queen is Dead" by Michael Joseph Gross, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Bear Clipping: Melancholy and Abstraction, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Bear Clipping: Arno Breker, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Bear Clipping: "Not in Kansas Anymore: The Appeal of Oz for Gay Males" by Dee Michel, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Bear Clipping: "Whither went my Manhood?", 2007 (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Consciousness Article, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Bear Clipping: Survival of the Prettiest: The Science of Beauty by Nancy Etcoff, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - Bear Clipping: Bringing Up Boys by Dr. James Dobson, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - Bear Clipping: Bay Area Reporter Articles, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Bear Clipping: Rural Gays Articles, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - Bear Clipping: CruisingForSex.com, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 57)
    - Bear Clipping: Articles about Trans Women, 2006-2007 (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - Bear Clipping: Octobearfest, 1993, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Magazines and Newsletters, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Magazines and Newsletters, 2005-2008 (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - Bear Clipping: Gloss Magazine, 2007-2009 (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Magazines and Newsletters, 1994, 2000, 2003, 2006, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 63)
    - Bear Clipping: Ulrichs, Karl Heinrich, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 64)
    - Bear Clipping: Vigeland, Gustav, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 65)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project, 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 66)